Ah, so satisfied drinking.
Ah, so lazy to go home.
Just stay overnight, Suneo.
But Dekisugi also drank a lot, right?
I use the "Wake Up Soon"
gadget so I'm not drunk.
Me too.
Haha, you two are really boring.
Why drink if you wake up quickly?
Goodbye, Nobita!
Don't get lost on the road, OK.
Okay, Gian.
Yeah, but he's on auto-drive,
so there's no way to get lost.
That's right, hahaha.
Sorry, I can't come tomorrow.
There is a sudden work, right?
That can't be help.
Being an elite person
is indeed difficult, huh.
Bye, yes.
Goal: Go home. Go, scooter.
Tomorrow, don't be late, you know!
I know too!
Finally tomorrow comes the day.
His wedding day.
Even though he is just Nobita.
Doraemon...
We'll see the wedding
day next time, shall we?
Okay. Let's hurry back to our times.
I also want to meet Shizuka at my dinner.
Birthday, birthday!
I am home!
Mom, what's for lunch today?
Nobita!
I found this in your desk drawer!
Can't we talk about this later?
Today it's...
It is enough!
I'm not angry because you got zero points,
but because you hid this paper!
Mom didn't teach you
to be a child like that!
Why do you have to be mad
about this on summer vacation?
How embarrassing it really is.
Today is bad too, huh.
Even though you don't
have to be that angry.
Nothing can be done, right?
Because you're the one at fault.
But today is my birthday.
Could it be...
Oh, yeah. It must be!
Hah? What have you
been talking about earlier?
I am not the biological
child of this family.
They must have picked
me up from somewhere.
Hahaha, how stupid.
If I were their real child,
Mother wouldn't speak that badly!
After all, if I really am their son,
why did they name me Nobita?
Isn't that a common name, huh?
I want a cooler name!
Ah, where is my biological mother?
You're talking ridiculous.
What are you doing up there, Doraemon?
Oh, I'm checking my magic gadgets.
If the floor is messy, so I use this
Gravity Paint to work on the ceiling.
Now, lots of it, huh.
Nobita, don't hold it
carelessly, you know. I just
want to test whether these
gadgets are damaged or not.
Uh, don't touch it carelessly!
What is that?
This is the "Stick of Forgetfulness".
If we use this stick, we can
forget what happened before.
Eh?! If you hit Mom
using that stick earlier,
she doesn't have
to be angry like that.
I wont use this wand
for something like that!
Don't say that, please.
I want to borrow it.
Instead of that, you
better study harder,
so you don't need to
get another zero score.
How can I be!?
See! There is more!
Already collected a lot, huh.
Please, lend me that gadget!
If not, please hide this in
your magic pocket, please!
Cannot!
How it come to this?
If she see this, surely...
This is from the future department store.
What is that?
Sometimes, they like to send
sample items like this one.
Oh, I see?
Let us see
Soul Swapping Ropes?
Wait, again, you just grabbed it!
Changing.
Exchange completed.
Whoa, what is this? Very weird!
So this rope can be used to turn us into
someone else who also holds this rope.
I became Doraemon!
Hm, hm, so that's how it is.
If we use the rope one more time...
Back to normal.
Oh, so this is it!
If so, can we not take it back one more
time, so I won't be nagged by Mother?
Don't talk carelessly!
You really can't, can you?
Nobita! Nobita? Nobita!
Oh, is that so?
Are you alright?
Hahaha, it worked!
Are you alright? Nobita!
Yes, I'm fine.
I have to hurry and save both of us.
Nobita! Nobita!
Where the hell is he?
Eh? Me why?
Suddenly they drove me
here on a time machine.
Who?
You and I!
Hey Nobita, I do not understand
at all what you are talking about.
But I can only. Say that.
Hm, I don't understand.
Looks like something happened somewhere.
Yeah, but now I'm here,
so no problem, right?
Really, you are so relaxed!
What's more important is this!
We have to find a place
to hide, so it won't be found!
Rather than that, wouldn't it
be easier if you just studied?
You are very talkative, Doraemon.
Nobita, go shopping for a while.
It's Mother!
There is something that I want you to buy.
Just recently, mom said you too much.
Eh? Very weird.
I thought he was here. Where did he go?
It's very dangerous.
Oh, I found a great place!
This way it's safe.
Oh? It's..
Wow, I missed you so much!
This teddy bear that I
loved when I was little.
Lots of patches, huh?
Yes, Grandma fixed this.
You have Grandma?
She died when I was in kindergarten.
This is it!
The person who's Nobita hugging, right?
Looks like the person
is very friendly, huh.
Grandma always spoiled me.
Gian... Gian broke my doll!
Wow, what a pity.
This, in this way, the
bear is no longer sick.
Grandma!
Whoa, walah...
Nobita is really a spoiled child.
So you've been whiny and
spoiled from then on, huh?
What I want to talk about is
Grandma's kindness and warmth!
Listen carefully, please!
Sorry Sorry!
Hah? Why, Nobita?
I want to meet...
Hah?
I want to see Grandma one more time!
If you say that too..
Oh yes! If we use a time
machine, we can go back in time.
Better not.
Why not?
If Grandma saw that you suddenly became
an adult, what do you think would happen?
Surely he will be
shocked and fall and slip!
If we talk carefully, she will understand!
You think you can understand time machine!?
But, but...
Oh yes! How about we just look from afar?
We can hide somewhere.
After seeing her for a while,
come back straight home, huh?
Hooray!
Let's go!
Wait a minute!
We go back to when I was 3 years old.
We're leaving, here.
Okay!
Wow, I missed you so
much! Home in the past!
There's still a litter box!
Oh, Persimmon fruit tree!
Two years ago, this tree was cut down.
Nobita, if anyone sees us it could be
dangerous. Hurry and look at Grandma!
Oh yes.
Grandma is always in this room.
Remember, yes. Well only see her from afar.
You know?
Nothing. What's on the second floor?
This door has always been jammed.
If it can't be pulled, try to push it.
Who are you?
Now, so young!
Is it true?
But 7 years later, her face
became covered with wrinkles.
Yes yes.
What the hell are you guys going
into someone's house! Get out there!
Even though it's me. Doesn't she know?
How could she possibly know?
Looks like Grandma went out.
That was me when I was 3 years old!
How cute. The one now isn't cute at all.
What the heck?
Nobita, don't cry.
It's Shizuka!
Let's play house.
Come on, I'll take you home.
Nobita is very whiny, huh.
I took the candy.
Why are you making fun of me?
Stop it. They're just kids!
Yesterday they pushed me down at school!
Don't mix the past with the present!
Grandma!
Grandma is alive...
Grandma is alive... Grandma is walking...
Dad, go to work first, okay.
Okay, be careful.
Here's your lunch.
Thank you.
Wow, wow...
Nobita and Shizuka are very close, huh.
Grandma!
Have you bought fireworks, haven't you?
Forgive me. Grandma has
been around to all the toy stores.
But they only sell fireworks in summer.
Don't want, don't want!
Forgive me.
You don't sulk like that, please.
I want fireworks!
Yes, sorry, yes.
Shut up! I hate Grandma! Get in the house!
Yes yes.
I don't like Nobita like that!
Hey, me! Don't be so
mean to Grandma, please!
What are you doing?
Why are you teasing my son?
Um, er... all of this has a reason...
Reason?
Actually I am Nobita.
Nobita is this kid, you know.
No, I'm from the future...
What a pity...
What a freak.
That's not it... Wait!
See? How could they believe.
Satisfied, right?
You saw Grandma, let's go home.
Okay, let's go.
Once again!
Ah, you were that weird kid earlier!
Mother!
Is he really here?
Geez, to enter the house.
How scary.
Here, here.
Whose child is he?
Grandma, did a strange
child come into this room?
No.
Hah?
Seriously, where is he hiding, huh?
How about this? Do I
have to go to the police?
Thank you.
Grandma, don't you suspect me?
No.
Grandma, do you really love Nobita?
Yes, of course.
If possible, Grandma wanted
to always be by his side.
But no way, huh? Grandma is already old.
Don't talk so pathetic!
At the very least, Grandma
wants to see him get to school.
Seeing him wearing a
backpack and going to school...
Want to see it just once.
Wait a minute, please!
I have to wait until when? Damnit!
Doraemon! Backpack, backpack!
What the heck? Backpack?
I want to get my backpack!
Backpack, backpack!
Just stop it already!
Grandma.
Oh...
Maybe you doesn't
believe it, but I'm Nobita.
That is true.
From earlier Grandma thought so too.
You believe it?
Don't doubt it at all?
Who doubts Nobita's talk?
Grandma!
There, there. You are so spoiled, huh.
After seeing you in elementary
school, Grandma thought.
Grandma wants to see your bride just once.
I understand, Grandma.
I'll show my bride to you.
Wait for me, yes, Grandma.
Nobita.
Doraemon!
Grandma believes you!
Yes! Look, I want to show
Grandma a look at the future.
But is it alright, making
a promise like that?
The future can still change!
But recently we saw my future, right?
We can't say for sure that you
are 100% going to marry Shizuka.
Oh yes. Time Television!
Take out Time Television!
Yes yes.
The wedding venue was at
the Prince Melon Hotel, right?
Is it alright?
It can't be. Not connected, here.
If he doesn't come quickly
it could be bad, right?
What is Nobita doing, anyway?
Ah, that's right!
Until the last second it was too late.
How pathetic.
He couldn't not have come, could he?
But there are stories, where the bride
and groom run away on their wedding day...
No way, right?
Nobita... Nobita, is everything okay?
Grandma!
Good afternoon, I am Doraemon.
Yes, good afternoon.
Doraemon who brought me here.
If so, thank you, yes, good raccoon.
I'm not a raccoon, you know.
Grandma wait a little longer, yes.
I will definitely meet
Grandma with my bride.
Isn't it a hassle?
Grandma has made strange wishes.
It is okay. I just need a little more time.
A little bit more! But
there is no problem, really.
Oh, I see? Then just slow down.
Okay!
Grandma will wait here.
We'll be home soon!
Let's go to wedding day!
It's about you, so we don't know
what problem you created this time.
Ah, it's raining.
Nobita, hurry up!
Okay!
Let's hide there.
Maybe he got lost inside the hotel.
Maybe. Let us find!
Come on, let's follow them.
Shizuka!
I can't just stand by.
How beautiful!
Just leave it to us!
Where's Nobita?
Sorry, Shizuka. Also sorry to your parents.
It is okay. We're just worried.
Let's go there, get closer.
Okay.
Where is the boy?
Even though he came out before us.
As long as there is no accident, it's okay.
But that kid was so careless.
There is currently no news of
any accidents around here at all.
I wonder why, Nobita?
Um, it looks like you guys are worried.
But the time is near...
Geez, why didn't he come?
So it's true. He didn't have
confidence in himself, so he ran away.
It can't be that!
Nobita will definitely come!
What is this? How about this?
Troublesome for everyone like this...
Will the marriage be canceled?
Do something, please, Doraemon!
Only you can replace, right?
Before you have to wear
this and become an adult.
No, no, I can't!
There is only this way!
I can't!
Get caught!
I will follow you, really.
I don't understand anything about marriage!
Nobita!
Nobita! What are you doing until this time?
Nobiita, are you okay? What happened?
Um...
Oh yeah, l-l got lost on the way.
That's right.
He really is Nobita.
Come on, everyone in the
party room. Please enter.
Please.
"Small Light".
Hey, look at that.
Nobita's teeth are grinding.
Is it alright?
I'm here, really.
That's very worrying.
Start, that's it.
Nobita, do you vow to marry Shizuka
and love her in good times and bad times?
Vow to be with her until the end?
Nobita, do you swear?
Are you alright?
Ah, his head is empty.
What should I do?
Oh yes!
Oh, sorry!
It's fine.
I swear!
Is it okay if I do it?
The real one didn't come,
so it can't be helped, right?
It feels so weird!
Now is the time for our bride
and groom to kiss each other.
Kiss?
Nobita?
Wow, all this can be eaten, right?
Nobita, you are really relaxed,
after making a fuss like that.
How delicious!
Hey, Nobita.
If you are too excited you
can get caught, you know!
Congratulations, yes, Shizuka.
Thank you.
Did I catch a cold, okay?
Everyone, please pay attention.
Our bride and groom are
going to cut the cake now.
First, let's make the
cake here. Please watch it.
Those who want to see
closely are also allowed.
Let's go.
I couldn't believe it had rained suddenly.
But it's okay. This is a gardening
party room with a see-through roof.
We are given the use of this room because
the owner is an acquaintance of my father.
Great! Great!
Looks delicious.
Hugh!
The cake is finished, please cut it.
'Hah?
What is wrong?
There is only one knife, you know.
What are you saying?
We'll both hold the knife.
Hehe, that's right, yeah.
Nobita, cut it quickly!
This cake cutting will be the first
activity the couple will do together.
Nobita, look here, please!
Nobita, Shizuka,
congratulations on your marriage.
Even though you can only
get 0 points in the past...
I'm happy you can be a good
man and get married today.
Now, marriage is really fun, huh...
Oh, right, Shizuka became suspicious.
Eh, really?
Now, let us hear the remarks from
our groom, Nobita Nobi.
Oh, okay, remarks, right?
Good afternoon!
Ah? Why? What is wrong?
Not good afternoon.
You've thought about the speech, right?
Eh? Speech?
Oh, yeah, so you mean that, huh?
Where will I put it?
I don't know, you know.
If I'm not mistaken... here, right?
No, this is it?
There can't be.
Oh yes!
Hahaha, how could I forget that...
Looks like I left it in the waiting room.
I'll take it first, yes!
! 11 Looks like our groom
has to get ready first.
Let's wait.
We're really sorry...
The bride and groom are such a pain.
Wait a minute, give me the mic.
Everyone! While waiting
for Nobita to return...
I, as his best friend,
will sing for all of you.
Hey... Wait... Sorry, huh...
Gian, let's go back to the seats.
Shut up, leave me alone!
Let's just have a drink.
Music, start!
Buttobasu denjarasu!
Am strong and dangerous!
Ore Gian!
I am Gian!
Ittoushou. Addokkoishou! I beat everyone!
What are you doing? Gian is singing!
Even here too, the singing
can break your head!
The only way we have
is to find my adult self!
At this rate, the wedding
party could be ruined!
Nobita, go back quickly!
I can't! I don't know
what greeting speech is!
You just need to talk
about yourself, right?
I can't! We have to find the grown me!
By the way, isn't the greeting speech
"Good Morning" or "Good Afternoon", huh?
In a place like that, greeting
means thanking your parents.
Be thankful? They Always
get mad when I get 0 points!
Impossible impossible!
You're still talking about that.
He's nowhere.
Oh, yeah, let's just use the search stick.
What is that?
The stick can be a signpost
for the person we want to find.
Heh, very practical.
Why?
Remember when we came here?
Tidying up magic gadgets.
You were in a hurry, I was
panicking too, that's why I missed a lot.
How about we go back to the
original world and take it first?
We don't have time.
Don’t worry.
For example, we leave at 2.
We go back to the origin
and waste 1 hour there.
Keep going back to the future.
When we go out we put it in 5
minutes, so it's 2 past 5 o'clock.
Finally we only waste 5 minutes.
Doraemon, you are so smart.
Not really, ah.
Let's go to the time machine place.
Okay!
Ah! That's right...
There he is!
Geez, just make people
worry. He didn't fall asleep, right?
It is nothing.
Do not tell me...
W-Wait! Where are you going?
Toilet!
Are you dying?
Don't talk stupid like that!
This isn't the one!
Nothing! Nothing!
Nothing! Nothing! Nothing!
Nothing! Nothing! Nothing! Nothing!
It's not anywhere!
What happened?
The time machine was taken by someone!
By whom?
There is only one person who
can drive a time machine today.
Your adult self!
Geez, haphazardly riding time machine.
Did he go to another era?
Your adult self.
But why?
I do not know? He is you!
Don't you have any ideas?
I do not know?
He's me from the future.
Ah... no him, not you.
Nobita is always like that.
Forgive me.
What is wrong?
So we can't go home from this era?
This has happened before.
You can do something, right?
Everything will be all right, right, Doraemon?
Oh yes! What about the Time Belt?
I told you...
Being tidied up.
Everything that could help
us get home was left behind.
How about it, Doraemon?
Well, we have to live
in this era like this...
am hungry.
Surely everyone has come
home from the party venue.
Everything must be messy.
Of the gadgets here, is there anything that
can be used to return home or not, huh?
This is it! We can use this!
"Soul Time Machine"!
"Soul Time Machine"?
This gadget will absorb your soul
and send it to you in a different era.
With this, we can send your
soul to the moment before we left.
At that time, the time
machine was still there, so you
could use the time machine
and come back here, right?
If you try it, you will understand.
Please, yes, Nobita!
Hey, if we do it one more time, don't
you the one who will be nagged by Mother?
Don't talk carelessly!
Nobita! Nobita! Nobita!
Oh, so it's like this, huh?
Are you alright?
It worked!
Are you okay, Nobita?
Yes I'm fine.
I have to hurry and save both of us.
Nobita? Nobita!
Is he all right?
Looks like he's taking a nap.
This is indeed hobby, hahaha.
Ah, what a mess.
Doraemon!
Nobita!
I got the time machine!
Then, let's return it to normal, OK.
Okay.
It worked!
Eh? Me why?
I have two?
This is the future, right?
Stop it. Do not worry about it.
What is it?
Alright, really.
Hey, why am I suddenly in the future?
Why there are two me?
Do not worry about it.
How could that be? Please explain!
Before it got complicated, we
made this Nobita forget about it.
This forgetful stick is useful too, huh.
Eh? Why am I here?
No, don't think about it.
Duh, where is he?
Hah? Me why?
They took me there on a time machine.
Who?
This way, we can rest easy.
Oh, no!
Nobita, go shopping for a bit!
It's Mother!
Hurry up and hide here!
Just recently, mom said too much.
If you're there, please answer...
Well, now... where is
the adult Nobita, huh?
What does it mean?
Nobita who has grown
up may exist in this era.
I have no reason to meet you guys.
Especially after I said
that half a year ago.
Do you want to meet Doraemon?
No, I don't have to.
Doraemon is your friend...
my friend when I was little.
Oh yes!
What's wrong?
By the way, why did you
run away from the wedding?
Don't you like Shizuka anymore?
How could that be!
I like her! I really love her!
Being able to marry
Shizuka is truly a dream.
But?
But what?
Yesterday, after
drinking with friends and I
was alone, I was
thinking about the future.
Then, I got scared
Afraid... Afraid... So scared!
Afraid of what?
Since I'm like this, maybe I
can't make Shizuka happy!
Why are you so weak?
After all, you also know why
Shizuka wanted to marry me, right?
She felt that I was unreliable.
Nobita has not changed at all, huh.
If we let it go, we don't know
what will happen, I get worried.
1 understand.
If she married me for a reason
like that, pity Shizuka herself!
She's too kind.
So that's why you came back to this time?
At that time, I happened
to go to a public toilet.
Why is there a time machine here?
I don't care where the machine
takes me. I just want time to think.
The reason I return
to this time is because
the time machine is
set to return to this time.
So that's the reason you left the wedding?
Don't you think you've
been a bother for everyone?
Don’t worry. When I got more confident, I
would go back to my wedding party, really.
If that's the case, I also know...
Could it be, have you seen it?
I'm not coming back?
That's why we are looking for you.
What happened?
1 don't know!
When the wedding started, you were gone!
Then the wedding?
I replaced you.
But in the middle I also ran away.
The marriage must have gone awry.
What are you doing?
But why?
Suddenly I didn't feel confident, you know.
So sad?
Didn't you come back
because of an accident?
Then what, then?
What kind of accident?!
Can't you forget Nobita?
I don't know why he disappeared suddenly.
Even though he said he liked me.
Seriously, Nobita. If I find
him, I'll beat him black and blue.
But I believe, Nobita
will definitely come back.
And when he comes back, he'll
tell me everything. I believe it.
I'm sorry, Shizuka! But
understand! I'm doing this for you too!
Take out your courage and come back.
I can not. If time has
passed any minute,...
...surely Shizuka would forget
me and meet another man.
If she forgets me, she can be happy.
Then, do you want to
see Shizuka's future again?
No. I don't want to see
Shizuka happy with another man!
How selfish.
But if she turns out to be unhappy,
I don't want to look anymore!
How troublesome this guy is.
He's you after all.
Come to think of it, this is
all because you are usually
just taking naps, which
is why I became like this.
Homework is not even
done, and tests can be 0 only.
Have no confidence anymore.
Don't blame me, please!
Don't fight with yourself!
Ah, if I could go back to this
time, maybe I could fix things up.
If you want, it's easy, really.
"Soul Swapping Ropes"!
If you hold this rope,
you can change bodies.
Why are you so excited?
It's Dangerous, you know.
Besides, when are you coming
back? Just now you still weren't around.
Now, how happy. This feeling and that...
No, nothing.
I'll play first, OK!
Ah, Nobita, the shopping...
It was out suddenly.
Wow, Gian and the others are still kids.
Of course, hahaha.
Hey, how are you?
What are you doing, Nobita? Very arrogant.
Even though you are Nobita,
you really don't hesitate!
I also want to play, please.
Oh, it's the first time you
asked to enter yourself.
Okay, let's try it.
You want to play baseball yourself.
He must have been training hard and finally
become an expert at playing baseball.
Catch it fast!
Nobita, you understand, right?
Batter, out!
Even though he is an adult,
he still hasn't changed at all.
That's right, yes.
Nobita! What does this mean?
You asked yourself to come
in, why did it turn out like this?
Oh right, you're angry.
Of course you get angry.
What did you say?
We lost because of you, you know!
His sense of power
simply couldn't stand it.
Damn it!
No kidding!
This is it! This feeling!
He looks so happy. Adults
just can't be understood.
Well, if he's tired, he can
also go home by himself.
Nobita, with a body like that,
we better enter from the window.
Yes, that’s right.
Hey, finally you guys came
home. Where have you been?
Who are you?
Oh, sorry. I'm from the future
department store. My name is Nakameguro.
Oh, those of you who
like to give us samples.
Why are you here today?
Um, about the soul-swaping
rope I sent here...
I want to take it back.
Hah? Is there any problem?
Of course not!
That's the gadgets that we choose
carefully from the shop right away...
How could there be a problem...
Then why?
Um, that... about that..
Don’t worry. We'll
definitely return it, really.
Oh, thank you very much!
But wait a minute, okay.
We just used the rope for Nobita. If they
have exchanged it back, we will return it.
I'm actually a kid.
So what?
H-H-H-How long has it been
since you guys used that rope?
Hmm... how many minutes has it been?
Almost 1 hour, right?
W-W-W-W-W-W-W-What!
Hah?
This is bad!
Listen carefully.
Actually, the gadget has
a slight error in its design...
After 1 hour, their
consciousness will disappear?
And the memories of both of us...
If you don't quickly
return to your original
self, the memories
will be lost forever.
Nobita!
Come on, quickly!
W-Where are .you going?
First of all we ask this gadget.
Where is the adult Nobita?
Why can't it?
What can I do, we just
search from here first.
Why? What is wrong?
Could it be... Nobita who has grown
up was not returning to the future..
Because he couldn't
go back to the future.,
What do you mean?
If he has lost his memory,
he doesn't know himself, right?
Then, my memories in this
era will also be lost, right?
It's a shame, but there you have it.
I don't want that!
Nobita, wait a minute!
Finally I am free from them,
and Suneo are so stubborn.
Excuse me.
Hey. Excuse me, you said?
Why are you angry?
It was just a little hit.
What's with this kid?
Why are you so arrogant?
Stop it, all of you.
He told us to stop...
You don't know, do you?
Oye, don't you have any
sense of apologies at all?
Y-yes.
What? Do you know what
usually happens at times like this?
N-No.
Don't know? Then I'll tell you.
Listen carefully, you know.
What about compensation money?
Compensation? How much?
Yes, 1000 yen.
Wait, because you are
arrogant, how about 2000 yen?
But this is not coercion, you
know. This is just a suggestion.
Hahaha, you junior high school student.
If that's all I can pay happily.
I always carry paper
money for times like this.
Take this.
Hah? Why is this money
has picture of Osamu Tezuka?
Alas, this is money from the future.
Did you take this money
from the children's bank?
Oye, don't mess around. Bring
out the real thing! Take it out!
Come on, get out the real money!
I can drive this vehicle, you know,
because I'm actually an adult.
Go, scooter!
Okay, scooter!
Hey, scooter!
In this era there is no
control of the sound, huh?
Then, how about we start the punishment?
Stupid brat...
My scooter!
Forgive me!
Dammit.
Hah?
Excuse me!
Forgive me!
Shizuka?
Hey, you...
Yes, you are interesting too.
Wait a minute. Come to think
of it, this is your fault, right?
You're just junior high school kids.
You can't do like this.
How can you threaten
adult who is older than you.
How could you be...
How could you avoid it!
Eh? Why just now?
How dare you. I can't forgive!
Take this!
It hurts... It's scary...
Geez.
Where is the adult Nobita?
Nobita!
It's very dangerous. Let's go down first.
Nobita, are you okay?
Who are you?
It's me, Doraemon! Just hold on!
That is true. I'm just stunned a little...
Your consciousness starts to
lose little by little! Nobita, hang on!
Hang in there, Nobita!
Don’t worry.
I will definitely restore
my future with Shizuka.
Nobita...
We don't have time. Come on, quickly!
You guys calm down, please.
It's your nature that makes us nervous!
Stop bothering weak people.
Who are you?
The kids in this town are all so arrogant.
If you don't step aside
it can be dangerous.
Shizuka, run away!
Why?
Get away from Shizuka!
Nobita!
You are!
Hah? Again, again...
My head is dizzy...
It felt like he was so hard to hit!
That's not the case...
You can't run away!
Gian?
So you ran off here, didn't you, Nobita?
You!
If this toy is damaged, you
have to compensate, you know.
Suneo!
Who are you?
The only ones allowed to
beat Nobita are us, you know!
Just remember, yes!
You're great too, Nobita.
You are so sloppy, huh.
Even though you can't fight.
Did 1 protect Shizuka?
Hooray!
Nobita? Why? Just hold on!
Nobita got on a scooter earlier and fell.
What?
Maybe he hit his head.
Bad, bad, bad, bad, bad, bad, bad, bad!
Hang in there, Nobita!
Don’t worry.
We will surely find my adult myself.
I will protect my future with Shizuka...
Nobita! Ah, Nobita!
How about this? At this rate,
Nobita will lose his memory!
Where is the adult Nobita? Damnit!
How about this? Is there
no gadget that can be used?
Oh yes! There is this!
Go to where adult Nobita is!
He's not an adult Nobita currently...
Ah, what should I do? What should I do?
Wait a minute.
If I say more carefully, will it work?
Go to little Nobita's place
where there is an adult Nobita!
Nobita! Nobita!
Oye, hang on, Nobita!
We've called an ambulance!
Hooray, it worked!
Who is it?
Do not ask.
Just put this rope on that Nobita.
Okay!
He can't go back.
What happened?
Just try it first!
Don't say you can't!
But the mechanism was set up like this...
I said try it first! If Nobita doesn't
come back, I'll crush you to pieces!
Even if you say so...
Do not give up!
If we don't try it, we won't know, right?
A-Alright. Geez, using the
rope is very rough, though.
See. The time has been
too long, so he can't go back.
Shut up!
Hold on...
I can't do it...
What happened?
Nobita, do you want this?
Your memories of Gian, Suneo,
and Shizuka will be lost, you know.
Really? You're kidding, right?
You're kidding, right?
Nobita, you will forget me too.
Do you want that?
I do not want!
Oh, It's moving!
We made it in time.
Nobita!
Nobita! Nobita!
Shizuka?
Geez! Nobita, you idiot!
Why are you fighting,
even though you can't?
Don't force it.
Let it be what you are!
Are you alright?
Yes. I think I can go home.
Yes. Looks like I've been able
to go back to my Shizuka's place.
But before returning to the future,
there is one place I want to visit.
Because I have to make a
speech at the wedding, right?
Could it be, you want to go to...
Yes, our
Yes, our birthday!
That's right. I also want to make sure that
I really am the child of this family,...
...and why they gave me the name Nobita.
I also want to know.
Okay, okay. It's been this
far, I just follow your wishes.
Wow, this was my house 10 years ago!
At that time, this room
was still Father's room.
Looks like we've stolen her hobby room.
There are no blisters on the pillars yet.
But there's nobody here.
If my parents are not here, how am I born?
Could it be that you are
really an adopted child?
See. That is right!
Calm down, they must be in the hospital.
Where is she? Where is she?
Oh, Dad! 10 years younger!
From my point of view,
he's 25 years younger!
Still like a young man.
Who are you?
You forgot your own son!
Do not say like that!
You weren't born here!
Excuse me, it looks like
we are at the wrong house.
What is that?
Instead of thinking about
that, where is the baby, huh?
Even though I was home early from work.
Ah, where? Where? Here, huh?
Isn't he at the hospital?
Oh yes! That is true!
In such a hurry.
By the way, where is the hospital?
Wait a minute! We're coming too!
Congratulations, sir! Your son is born.
Oh, thanks for the food!
No, I mean... thank you.
Come here.
Huh, I'm so excited.
I'm excited too.
What type of baby that be?
Must be a cute kid like us.
Hahaha, it's better not
to get your hopes up.
Tama-Chan!
Hello, this is Dad, son!
How cute he's. This is my son, right?
Hello, my baby!
1 want to see too!
Is this me?
Why are there wrinkles like
this? Looks like a monkey!
What do you mean monkey, huh?
That was shocking. Don't be that angry too.
He's mad because you
weren't being polite, right?
After all, isn't baby Nobita cute?
No! Not cute at all!
Surely that baby is not me!
Newborn babies are like that, you know.
Who are those kids?
They've been following me from earlier.
I wonder what their parents look like.
Where's my mom, by the way?
She should be with you, right?
Oh, she said she wanted
to tell our ancestors.
She must be very happy, huh?
Yes, she couldn't stop crying.
This bear?
Mother's gift for this child.
Too fast, right?
By the way, what about this child's name?
I thought about it carefully.
What is that?
Tadaaa, I'm telling you, yes.
Nobita Nobi!
Nobita?
Nice name, right?
I want a cooler name.
They should listen to our hopes, please.
Stop it, stop it. You'll be
scolded again, you know!
The meaning of the
name? Of course there is!
I want this child to
grow up healthy always.
What a nice name.
Nobita Nobi.
I like that name.
So they thought about the name carefully.
I want to raise him to be a good boy.
He must be a good boy!
If he looks like you,
he will be doing well.
If he looks like you, he
will be good at sports.
Truly.
You only looks alike in the
weak spots of your parents.
What a chatterbox, ah!
Is he going to be a professor?
Or a baseball player?
He can be a painter too.
Painter, sculptor, musician.
Anything is okay.
As long as he is of
use to those around him.
Care for others and be brave.
A cheerful child, a real boy,
strong, fair, and handsome.
Um, don't get your hopes up, anyway.
He's not that great kid, really.
From earlier you kept bothering me.
Do you have a grudge against my son?!
Father and mother
They are very happy.
They are full of hope.
Let's go back to the future.
Finally we are back.
Oh, come here.
What? What?
Why?
Look at that.
In a place like that, greeting
means thanking your parents.
Be thankful? They always get
mad when I get 0 points! I can not!
You're still thinking about it.
To run like that...
Come on, quickly.
Um... sorry, yeah. But can you go alone?
We still have important
promise that we must keep.
Right, Doraemon?
Oh, I see?
If so, this is goodbye.
Thank you for finding me.
Thank you for finding me.:
Your future is mine too.:
Oh yes! This.
This...
See you later, yes!
By the way, what is that important promise?
Thanks for waiting!
Thank you!
Everyone, my healthy
friend, Nobita, is back!
Thank goodness, we survived.
Thank you, Nobita!
Really grateful!
But it took him a long time to come back.
I've bought time for you, you know.
Welcome back.
I am back.
You must be worried, right?
Not really.
Not at all.
Then, let us hear the Greeting
remarks from our groom once again.
The rain has stopped.
Everyone, good afternoon. I am Nobita Nobi.
We know already!
At first, I didn't like this name.
Because it seems slow and stupid.
But when I was born, my
parents gave me this name
in the hope that I will
continue to grow.healthily.
Now, I really like this name.
It's like he was there and saw
everything that was going on, huh?
I was raised by my
parents and my grandma...
And also my grandma, they
took care of me with great love.
When I was a kid and came home
crying, Grandma always comforted me.
And Grandma always believed what I said.
When I got zero points,
Mom always scolded me.
And Father taught me
to try to reach my dreams.
I grew up with your love.
And Shizuka's father...
You once said that I am a person who
understands the pain of other people.
It's because my family taught me that.
Maybe I did not become the child my
parents and grandma expected me to be.
Maybe they expected me to
become a painter or a baseball player.
Wow, their hopes all failed!
You're so loud!
But I can say this one thing.
I've been raised by a wonderful family.
Because of that, even
though it can't be expected,
.. I want to make a
warm family with Shizuka.
In this regard, I am very confident.
If I do that, I feel I have returned the
services of my parents and grandma.
Mother, father.
Shizuka's Father and Mother.
We will follow in your footsteps;
Shizuka.
Let's make a happy family like them.
What is wrong?
No, nothing.
Are you going home already?
Grandma has seen enough.
Looks like Mom was here just now.
Oh, you feel so too?
It's -possible that Mom actually came here.
Nobita.
Your earlier was fake, right?
That... er...
Even though you are better off just you.
You always hide your own sadness...
But in the end, you must be
helped by Doraemon again, right?
I came back for the sake of my happiness.
With that, Shizuka must also be happy.
Very good!
Oh yes. This.
I want to start all over again.
OK, we're going home?
Nobita,
You really did fulfill Grandma's dream.
Thank you.
You're welcome. I'm also grateful for being
able to keep my promise to my grandmother.
Yes. Grandma is really very happy.
But...
In order to keep Grandma's promise...
You must have suffered a lot
just to keep Grandma's promise.
That whiny little Nobita...
To end up being a good boy like this.
That's what made Grandma the happiest.
Grandma!
I'm not like that.
I'm a stupid coward,
also a crybaby...
But Nobita has real strength, right?
Shizuka must know that too,
that's why she became your bride.
Grandma!
Oh, oh, you're back to
being little Nobita again.
Can I come again?
You can come no matter how many times.
Grandma will be waiting for you here.
So the time machine can drive itself, huh?
Yes. I'm tired of driving today.
So many things happened.
It's you, really.
Hehehe. Sorry, yes, Doraemon.
Are you really sorry?
Of course! It's true!
Really?
How stubborn, huh!
Oh, damn it! Forgetful Stick!
This is bad! Nobita forgot his memory.
This is really bad, right?
But wait!
Nobita, Nobita, Nobita...
Doraemon?
Why am I riding a time machine?
You see, we have just
experienced something very
troublesome, but also
something very beautiful.-
Eh? What is that? What
is that? Please, tell me!
When you grow up, you will know.
Until then, it's better if you don't Know.
Why is that? What happened?
How much do you remember?
Hmm, we met Grandma...
Oh yes! We have to show
my .bride to Grandma!
Take it easy. Everything is finished.
Eh? What does it mean? Tell me please!
How stubborn, huh! I won't tell!
Please, Doraemon!
♪ "It's okay to cry" ♪
♪ Those words have saved me ♪
♪ Thank you ♪
♪ I am pathetic and careless, ♪
♪ But when I think of you,
my tomorrow will shine ♪
♪ It's okay if we are what we are ♪
♪ Let's find a bright
place and play together ♪
♪ There is a little rainbow on the soles of
your feet that is watering the veranda ♪
♪ Hey... ♪
♪ I will be by your side
forever and always be here ♪
♪ I will fight so that we
don't split up forever ♪
♪ I won't let go of this
hand so I don't lose you ♪
♪ Mother's kindness and
Father's wittiness are like us ♪
♪ Our future will be bright ♪
♪ It's okay if your dreams aren't big ♪
♪ Just be you ♪
♪ When you are alone and
lost, just remember that day ♪
♪ That sad night, give me half of it ♪
♪ I want you to laugh on a nice day ♪
♪ Words like anything won't be enough ♪
♪ Maybe because I touched your warmth ♪
♪ About family, friends and myself ♪
♪ Always laughing, so want to cry ♪
♪ Something is shining in this empty sky ♪
♪ I'm always looking for words
that can replace "Thank you." ♪
♪ I will be by your side
forever and always be here ♪
♪ I will fight so that we
don't split up forever ♪
♪ I won't let go of this
hand so l don't lose you ♪
♪ I won't let go ♪